http://www.eliesaab.com/en/terms-and-conditions

ELIE SAAB
When you browse on this site, you agree to the use of cookies that allow proposing services and offers to match your centers of interest and enable the establishment of visit statistics. To know more about configuring cookies,
click here.
My wishlist
product(s)
READY-TO-WEAR
AUTUMN / WINTER 2020-2021
HAUTE COUTURE
SPRING SUMMER 2020
READY-TO-WEAR
PREFALL 2020
READY-TO-WEAR
SPRING/SUMMER 2020
General terms and conditions
The www.eliesaab.com website has been designed by UZIK (80, rue du Faubourg St-Denis 75010 Paris, France) - www.uzik.com - Tel.: +33 1 40 26 75 33HostingThe www.eliesaab.com website is hosted by WAYCOM 2, rue des Bourets - 92150 Suresnes.Use of the Elie Saab website accessible at www.eliesaab.com as well as web pages accessible through the Elie Saab website, including pages on third party networking services (the "Site") is subject to the following legally binding terms and conditions ("Terms") and constitutes your agreement to be bound by and to act in accordance with these Terms.
We reserve the right to change the Terms at any time and you agree to be bound by such changes.1. Privacy PolicyPlease read our Privacy Policy below, which governs the manner in which we will handle any personal information that you provide us.2. Ownership RightsELIE SAAB FRANCE and/or its worldwide affiliates ("Elie Saab") own all right, title and interest in and to the Site and/or own the contents and applications on the Site (including on social network websites).Elie Saab owns or is licensed to use all copyrights for all materials on the Site. Elie Saab also owns or is licensed to use all trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos and domain names used on or in connection with the Site. Any modification or use of the materials from the Site for any purpose not explicitly permitted by Elie Saab is a violation of Elie Saab's copyright and other proprietary rights.No part of the Site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed in any manner whatsoever, except for viewing purposes, without the prior
written consent of Elie Saab.3. Disclaimer/Limitation on LiabilityUse of and browsing of the Site are at your own risk. Neither Elie Saab nor any party representing or otherwise affiliated with Elie Saab in creating or presenting the Site are liable for any direct or indirect damages arising out of your use of the Site. To the extent permitted by law and without limiting any of the foregoing, everything on the Site is provided to you without warranty, either expressed or implied.Solicited information that you submit to Elie Saab through the Site are subject to our below Privacy Policy. All unsolicited reviews, comments or other submissions, including ideas, concepts, techniques, know-how and the like, shall not be treated as confidential by Elie Saab and Elie Saab may use such materials in any manner that it deems appropriate. For more information on this topic, please see our below Privacy Policy.4. LinksElie Saab is not responsible for third party websites that link to or from the Site. Elie Saab does not endorse any such sites or the goods or services offered on such sites. Elie Saab disclaims all responsibility for the accuracy of any of the information provided on such linked sites. Elie Saab shall not be held liable or responsible for the content of any sites that link to or from the Site.5. Accuracy of InformationElie Saab takes reasonable steps to ensure the accuracy of the information included in the Site. However, Elie Saab takes no responsibility for errors or omissions in the content of the Site and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness or timeliness of information provided on the Site. Information provided on the Site is subject to change at any time without prior notice.6. Applicable Law and JurisdictionAny dispute over the content or use of the Site shall be governed by the substantive laws of France, and the French courts shall be competent to settle any such dispute.7. Entire AgreementYou acknowledge and agree that these Terms, together with our Privacy Policy below, constitute the entire agreement between you and Elie Saab with respect to the use of the Site.BY USING THE SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR UNDERSTANDING AND AGREEMENT TO COMPLY WITH THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.Last Updated: May, 2017.© Elie Saab, All Rights Reserved.ELIE SAAB PRIVACY POLICYThis privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how ELIE SAAB FRANCE and/or its worldwide affiliates ("Elie Saab") collects, uses, discloses and store your information and is directed and applicable to individuals who visit those portions of the Elie Saab website accessible at www.eliesaab.com as well as web pages accessible through the Elie Saab website, including pages on third party networking services (the "Site").1. Collection and Use of Personal InformationPersonal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Elie Saab and/or the Site. Elie Saab and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. The type of information that we may collect include name, country, address, email address and phone number. The personal information we collect help us develop and improve our products, services and advertising.
From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis and research.2. Collection and Use of Non-Personal InformationWe also collect non-personal information – data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. It tells us such thing as how many users visited the Site and the pages accessed. Collecting this information helps us tailor our Site to our visitors.When you visit the Site to browse, read or download information, we automatically collect standard computer information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as you IP address, browser type and language, access time and referring website addresses. We generally do not link standard computer information to anything that will allow us to identify users, unless to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, Site, users or others.We also may collect non-personal information through cookies and other technologies. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us, for example, whether a user is a first time visitor or has visited the Site before and what areas of the websites are of greatest interest to the user. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information.If you want to disable cookies, please note that certain features of the Site may not be available.3. Disclosure to Third PartiesIt may be necessary – by law, legal process, litigation and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence – for Elie Saab to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. We may also disclose information about you if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm, financial loss or injury to, or interference with, our rights or property or the rights or property of our users or others, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.We may appoint third party service providers to administer and/or operate certain functions or services on our behalf, the proper performance of which may require a transfer of the information submitted by you. Any such transfer shall be subject to confidentiality and security obligations and for the sole purpose of the performance of this functions or services.We may also share your personal information with other third parties for joint marketing and promotions of products, services or events that may be of interest to you. Any transfers of personal information shall be subject to confidentiality and security obligations and for the sole purpose of the performance of those obligations.4. Unsolicited MaterialsThrough the Site, we request that you provide to us certain types of information so that we may better serve you. The requested information may include questions and comments about our products. Please do not provide us with materials, including but not limited to business, advertising, creative, marketing or any other types of proposals, concepts, know-how, ideas and the like ("Unsolicited Materials"). All Unsolicited Materials, including any unsolicited personal information (for example, personal information provided not in response to a specific request for such information, but in a free form text box), that we receive will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. By submitting any Unsolicited Materials, you agree that we shall have the sole discretion as to how to utilize such Unsolicited Materials and you automatically provide to us a perpetual, royalty free license to such end. If any Unsolicited Materials that you provide to us are protected by third party copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights, you agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Elie Saab and its respective officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, representatives, and third party providers against any claims or actions bought against any of these persons arising out of or relating to our use or possession of the Unsolicited Materials.5. SecurityYour privacy is important to us. However, we cannot secure that our level of security meets or exceeds any specific standards. No internet transmission is 100% secure or error-free, nor is stored data free from vulnerabilities. We cannot guarantee the security of our websites, databases or services, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet. We are not responsible for actions of third parties.6. CookiesA cookie is a file that saves Internet settings. It is stored by your browser when visiting a website for the first time. When you visit that site again, it can read the cookie to know if you have already visited it and possibly adapt its content. Cookies are useful to optimise your experience. This Website uses cookies to record information about your visits in order to compile anonymous statistics (audience measurement) on its traffic (the pages you visited, the date and time of visit, etc.). Cookies on this Website do not store your personal data.You can set the use of cookies on your browser, for example, their blocking, deletion or the selection of the cookies you accept or reject. You can delete cookies already stored on your computer. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser. The most common cookies can be set in the following menus:For Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0:1 Select the "Tools" menu then "Internet Options".2 Click on the "Privacy" tab3 Select the desired level using the cursor or click on the "Advanced" button to customise your cookie management.For Microsoft Internet Explorer 5:1 Select the "Tools" menu, then "Internet Options".2 Click on the "Security" tab3 Select "Internet" then "Custom Level4 Locate the "Cookies" heading and choose the option that suits youFor Netscape 6.X and 7.X:1 Choose the "Edit"> "Preferences" menu2 Privacy and Security3 CookiesFor Opera 6.0 and beyond:1 Choose the "File"> "Preferences" menu2. PrivacyFor Mozilla Firefox:1 Select the "Tools" menu2 Click on "Options"3 "Privacy" heading4 Cookies7. AmendmentsWe reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to amend or update this Privacy Policy at any time and you agree to be bound by such amendments or updates. We will notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting the revised policy with the date it was revised on this page. Your continued use constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.LAST UPDATED: May 2017SOURCESPictures of Beirut are the property of the Annahar Center For Documentation , Beirut, LebanonSee company structure here© Elie Saab, All Rights Reserved
dayshoursminutesseconds
Elie Saab
The bridal department
Points of sale
Careers
Contact
Terms and conditions
Terms and conditions
